<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>刍狗狗の小窝</title>
    <link>https://ydw.be/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 刍狗狗の小窝</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 21:30:04 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ydw.be/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Brain</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/shower/brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 21:30:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/shower/brain/</guid>
      <description>When aliens land on earth, mankind stops fighting with each other and finally becomes one. When there is a crisis, my brain also stops fighting and focuses on the crisis. Neurons are like mankind. Mankind are like neurons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wall</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 23:48:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/wall/</guid>
      <description>We were ejected out of the spaceship, now we are drifting in the universe. Sun is getting smaller and smaller, diminutive. The world is getting darker and darker.
A huge wall forms in front of us. The wall is bright, like a massive white screen. An apple suddenly came to my mind, the concept, the smell, the taste, the color, the nutrition of an apple are intertwined in my head, and bubble up from the bottom of my consciousness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2023</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 03:40:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/2023/</guid>
      <description>Time is flying or flowing.
We are dying. Alcohol isn&amp;rsquo;t doing us any good, it makes us feel the time being slower, but in reality it just slowly kills us.
We are living. A dog is barking in front of us, a chihuahua is jumping and barking at a huge dinosaur, fearlessly. We laugh at the chihuahua, but we&amp;rsquo;ve got a lot to learn from this little creature. We&amp;rsquo;ve become too accustomed to being a processor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 04:24:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/crazy/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t know why I am doing this, maybe it&amp;rsquo;s because I am crazy.
I am running around the square, no one cares.
I am running around the square, someone sees me.
I am running around the square, I feel wind.
I am running around the square, I wanna scream.
I am running around the square, I high five with every human I encounter.
I am running around the square, I have a QR code on my T-Shirt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/zen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 10:40:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/zen/</guid>
      <description>When you want to hurry something, that means you no longer care about it and want to get on to other things.
McDonalds, McKinsey, CNN, iPhone, Google, Moon landing, what are they?
Slow down. I want to start farming, but I don&amp;rsquo;t have a field. No need to hurry, let&amp;rsquo;s just steal some soil first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 03:40:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/2022/</guid>
      <description>Huh, 2021 finished, 2021 is certainly different than 2020, but how?
COVID-19 is still here, humans are still not extinct. We saw reports of different animals getting infected, but the virus doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be doing much to them, thank god.
When we drink water, water goes through us, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t stay, just like time. We are drinking the same water dinosaurs were drinking millions of years ago.
I saw a mummy, the hair and nails were like they are from yesterday, she is beautiful and probably was as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tears</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/tears/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 21:03:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/tears/</guid>
      <description>Communist, Donald Trump, Washington state, Washington, D.C., The falling man, H&amp;amp;M, Germany, Mao Zedong, God, Universe, You and Me.
All those moments will be lost in time, like tears in rain. Time to die.
An endless party is waiting for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 21:31:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/mind/</guid>
      <description>Mind is a weird concept. 1 21 guns, lay down your arms, give up the fight.
1 21 guns, throw up your arms, into the sky, you and I~
What shall I do to not give a fuck? I am too sensitive, too concerned, too worried, too sarcastic, too pessimistic about my life. I am giving too much fuck for living a good life which itself makes the life miserable. Maybe I should take a moment to forget/forgive myself and worry about climate change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 22:53:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/2021/</guid>
      <description>Fuck yeah, 2020 is finished.
I will miss you, you little, naughty, cute, cunt, crazy, badass, punk, pure, innocent virus.
I had a dream with you last night, it could be the new strain, the old strain, or a strain yet to come.
In the dream, the virus was in tears.
&amp;ldquo;I just want to have my children, my grandchildren, you know, it&amp;rsquo;s in my gene, like you guys.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Yes, I know, calm down, it&amp;rsquo;s not your fault.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>小偷</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/thief/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 19:59:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/thief/</guid>
      <description>我的父亲是一个小偷。
在深夜，我把他偷来的钱偷走，偷偷放回失主的口袋。
我也成了一个小偷。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 18:27:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/death/</guid>
      <description>I am dying, we are dying, the universe is dying. A comforting fact.
I don&amp;rsquo;t care if my soul still exists after I die, I don&amp;rsquo;t care if I go to heaven or hell after I die, I don&amp;rsquo;t care if you will miss me after I die, I don&amp;rsquo;t care if I will have another life after I die, I don&amp;rsquo;t care.
But I do like to imagine the death of our universe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joke</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/joke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 23:47:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/joke/</guid>
      <description>My jokes aren&amp;rsquo;t working out, but people laugh when my jokes aren&amp;rsquo;t working out, so my jokes are working out.
What a pathetic clown, I am not even a scary clown, I am just a harmless clown, a bug, a cookie, a bag of fine granulated sugar.
I am tired of telling not working out jokes, I want to be more important, maybe the president of the United State, a plumber, a writer, a reporter, a twitch just chatting host, a high school physics teacher, a prisoner, just not a clown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPv6 with DigitalOcean and WireGuard</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/boring/ipv6-wireguard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 23:11:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/boring/ipv6-wireguard/</guid>
      <description>My ISP doesn&amp;rsquo;t support IPv6 yet, I managed to have IPv6 connection by proxying through a DigitalOcean IPv6 server with WireGuard.
First, create a DigitalOcean droplet with IPv6 enabled.
According to the DigitalOcean IPv6 documentation, the subnet is /124, so it provides 16 IPv6 addresses to a droplet.
vim /etc/sysctl.conf
net.ipv4.ip_forward=1 net.ipv6.conf.all.forwarding=1 sysctl -p to load the /etc/sysctl.conf file.
Installing WireGuard according to https://www.wireguard.com/install.
On the DigitalOcean server, run
wg genkey &amp;gt; privatekey wg pubkey &amp;lt; privatekey &amp;gt; publickey On your client, also run the same commands to generate the private key and the corresponding public key (Your OS may have a WireGuard App that does it for you with clicking some buttons)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maggot</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/maggot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 00:37:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/maggot/</guid>
      <description>I have a trash can that becomes a fly base in the summer.
The shiny metallic color female flies always find a way to lay eggs inside the trash can. In no time the eggs become cute squirming larvas, then pupae, then flies that fly.
The stinky smell attracts the flies. Vinegar also attracts flies, because Acetic acid is produced when fruit ferments.
I take the trash bag out, squeeze the air out (which stinks), and tie the bag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/free/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 22:12:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/free/</guid>
      <description>Alcohol free means no alcohol.
Free alcohol means unlimited alcohol.
Drug free means no drug.
Free drug means unlimited drug.
What does love free mean?
What does free love mean?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 14:09:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/coffee/</guid>
      <description>I mistaken the salt for sugar and put it in my coffee. To my surprise it tasted quite good, so I recommended it to my friends, and they were amazed by the taste of the magical combination too. I quitted my job and opened a cafe selling salted coffee. Sugar is a taboo in my cafe. In a rainy midnight, while I was preparing to close the shop, a girl carrying loads of water drops came inside , and ordered a coffee with sugar and milk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chap2</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/island/chap2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 22:52:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/island/chap2/</guid>
      <description>小明坐在巴士里，司机默不作声。
可是司机平时不都是默不作声的吗？司机的工作是开车，又不是讲单口相声。此刻的小明却觉得不对劲，想跟司机搭话。
“嘿，司机师傅，请问还有多久到呀？”
司机并不回应，小明透过巨大的巴士车窗看到公路前方是一片巨大的漆黑，却不觉得害怕，脑子里还在想着为什么司机不说话。
巴士驶进了那片黑暗，世界变得一片漆黑，只有仪表盘发出的幽幽的蓝光，红光，绿光。这时司机回话了，“小伙子，我们抄个近路哈。”
巴士正在疯狂地下坠，乘客们像是在坐过山车，发出了各式各样的尖叫。经过近几年的交通安全整风运动，大家都有了系安全带的习惯。
在大家的尖叫声中，司机忽然发话了，这次是从巴士上的环绕声音响系统发出来的，这辆车与旅行社有合作，因为导游需要，所以车上配备了麦克风。
“大家都系好安全带了吧？“司机忽然打开了车内的照明系统，此刻的这辆巴士像是一架飞机，所有乘客头顶上方的LED灯都忽地同时打开。
大家看到司机并不在他的座位上，他面朝乘客们，手持一只麦克风，漂浮在空中。
“我们现在正在失重状态哦，像是一个自由下坠的电梯，空间站，从悬崖跳下被扔下的集装箱（里面还有人）。我们可以做点物理实验呢。“说着它便把麦克风缓缓松开，它还停在他嘴边，所以他的声音依旧能被采样，增益，清晰地传播到刚刚还在尖叫但是注意力已经被司机吸引的乘客们的耳边。
他掏出一块吃得很干净的T Bone，旋转了起来。T Bone的一端旋转了一会儿之后忽然跳到了另一边继续旋转，然后又跳回原点继续旋转(Tennis Racket Theorem)。乘客们觉得神奇，纷纷拿出自己身边的小物件也开始尝试，小明大概知道它的原理，与角动量，转动惯量等等性质有关，但具体的原理他也说不上来。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chap1</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/island/chap1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 22:52:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/island/chap1/</guid>
      <description>小明在房间里，这是一个非常干净的房间，有点宇宙飞船的感觉。房间里有一张单人床，一张桌子，两个椅子。小明坐在桌边的椅子上，另外一个椅子在门边，靠在床尾。
有人敲门，小明听见了，却不做任何反应。门自己打开了，小白径自进来了，把门关上，站在门边。小明转身望向门口的小白，先开口了，“我们该怎么办？”
小白走动两步，坐在床边的椅子上。“我不知道，这一切有点可怕。我们这是为了什么而活着啊？”
小明起身坐到了自己的床上，离小白很近，他握住了她的手，“我不知道，我想知道。”
小白把自己的手从小明的手里抽出，自言自语道，“未来究竟会怎么样呢？”
“哈哈，我猜不怎么样，可是现在的生活也不怎么样呢。”小明回答。
小明起身去了窗边。“如果我被宣判在这房间里生活一辈子，我还能够幸福吗？”
“可以的，在我们存在之前，人类不是被宣判在地球生活一辈子吗？地球不过是一个大一点的房间而已。我先走了。”小白走了。
小白走后，小明又坐回了他桌边的椅子。从侧面看，他长得像一个普通人，像是所有中国大学生的平均值，可是每个和他对视过的人，都会记住他的眼睛，他的眼睛很透明。
小明有点焦虑，他拿起了桌上的原子笔，随手抽了一张纸开始画了起来，此刻的他似乎并没有在思考，他希望用这种无意识的机械行为让自己的大脑休息一下，他称之为画画冥想。他并不知道冥想的定义，也并不想知道。他也将自己在房间里踱步的行为称为散步冥想，将自己在地板做俯卧撑叫作运动冥想，将自己看着窗外发呆称作看风景冥想。
外面下起雨了，淅沥沥的。小明不画画了，开始写字。
 啦啦啦，下雨啦。雨滴砸到地面上，发出可爱小声音，给人温馨的慰藉。
 雨能给人慰藉吗？晴天多了，会期盼雨水。雨天多了，会期盼阳光。
小明在纸上涂涂写写，心情似乎平静了一点，放下纸笔，去床边的洗漱台洗脸刷牙，他刷牙时看向窗外，有月亮，雨停了。
一天结束，小明躺下睡了。他躺着的时候不喜欢思考，但这不代表他但脑袋是一片空白，他会想一些固定枯燥乏味的画面。他顺着一个螺旋楼梯一直向下走，螺旋楼梯没有扶手，向螺旋楼梯中央的空洞底部看去只能一片纯粹的黑色。他不害怕，安静地向下走着，像只优雅的猫。走着，走着，走着，不知道自己走了多久，也不需要知道自己走了多久，走着，走着，他原本匀速的脚步变得忽快忽慢，世界变得拥有律动。他毫无征兆地向纯黑的洞中跳下，黑暗包围了他，他不害怕，因为他已经这么做过无数遍。螺旋楼梯没有尽头，螺旋楼梯的景象在快速下坠的他眼前快速闪烁，他睡着了。
对了，小明把这睡前的这段想象称作睡前冥想。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/island/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 22:47:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/island/intro/</guid>
      <description>我们是怎么落到这步田地的？城市，建筑，汽车，厕所，避孕套，水管工，妓女，程序员，火箭，政治，经济，同性恋，基督教，披萨，艾滋病，还有随便他妈的什么东西。
 这个疯狂的世界。
这就是我们被预设的命运吗？承载着同样的基因，人类还能做一些不同的事情吗？还是说不存在其他出路？
大多数科学家给出了一个负面的答案。他们说我们的社会像是一个活着的生物，像一个生物，它也通过着自然选择进行进化。现存的社会是进化的产物，在某种意义上说，现存的社会是最适合现在的时间，空间，人类，科技，环境的社会。现代猪是最适合现代社会的猪，现代社会是最适合现代猪的社会。
人类曾经做过一个生物圈二号实验，为了证明封闭生态系统在外层空间支持和维持人类生命的可行性。这本书的标题是岛，也像是一个封闭的系统。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rocket</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/rocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 00:24:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/rocket/</guid>
      <description>Space Shuttle Challenger.
That&amp;rsquo;s sad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doctor</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 00:01:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/doctor/</guid>
      <description>I need a doctor.
Does a doctor need another doctor? Does a barber need another barber? Does a teacher need another teacher? Does a husband need another husband? Does a president need another president? Does a vacuum cleaner need another vacuum cleaner?
I need a banana. I need some water. I need an apple.
Apple is an old fruit. When you eat an apple, you also digest the history. In the night, I imagine my ancestors, what&amp;rsquo;s inside the mind of my grandpa&amp;rsquo;s grandpa&amp;rsquo;s grandpa?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rapture</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/rapture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 23:02:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/rapture/</guid>
      <description>Rapture, ecstasy.
Jump! Let the blood flow, let the heart beat, let the brain lose its mind.
I wanna be dead!
Why don&amp;rsquo;t you kill me&amp;hellip;
You mean, painfulness is a part of life? I don&amp;rsquo;t know, man, my friend. I am in love with somebody. She is a robot, an air doll, a computer, artificial intelligence, regression, matrices, linear algebra, apple, salt, tonic water, condom, toilet paper, menstruation or copper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Command</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/boring/command/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 15:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/boring/command/</guid>
      <description>DNS nslookup -type=A google.com 1.1.1.1 host google.com 1.1.1.1 dig google.com Generate a test certificate for localhost openssl req -x509 -sha256 -nodes -addext &amp;#34;subjectAltName = DNS:localhost&amp;#34; -newkey rsa:2048 -days 365 -keyout localhost.key -out localhost.crt </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/shower/life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 22:38:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/shower/life/</guid>
      <description>How should we live our life?
 But do you think about this question when you are in a dream? You don&amp;rsquo;t question the meaning of existence in a dream. Because everything is so interesting and meaningless at the same time. You jump, you laugh, you stab someone, you talk, you murmur, you observe the sky, you sleep, you deep dive without breathing, you use every second, you are just immersed this bizarre dream world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bed</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/bed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 23:21:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/bed/</guid>
      <description>Beds and coffins are both made of wood, just that coffins have a lid.
I am tired of all these bullshit, my dear friend, sometimes I want to kill myself :( But I am not gonna commit it, no worries :)
Bed, womb, tomb, comb, coffin, iPhone, they seem to be the same thing to me. I hope I am not insane. I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to be a sane man. I want to be as normal as you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vodka</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/vodka/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 23:20:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/vodka/</guid>
      <description>In case you don&amp;rsquo;t know it, vodka can be put in the freezer. The melting point of ethanol is -114.14°C. When you pour frozen(I mean from the freezer, not literally frozen) vodka out, the liquid is sticky and together, interesting physics.
Drinking pure vodka is a bit boring, it tastes like alcohol and nothing else. D wants to make it more exciting, D bites his finger, and puts the bleeding finger in the glass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/bubble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 22:00:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/bubble/</guid>
      <description>We live in bubbles.
I was naive, I am naive, I will be naive.
I thought the brutality conducted by Hong Kong police was the result of the infiltration of PLA, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe that the local police would do those horrible things to their own innocent citizens. But that idea was challenged after watching the footages from the Minneapolis, New York, and other places in the US.
The police crush the crowd with their huge SUVs, they push the elderly down to the ground, they shoot the reporters, they beat the protesters, they worsen the situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hint</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/hint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 21:27:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/hint/</guid>
      <description>Life is full of hints.
Your cat has been hanging out lately. You have a window, your cat sneaks out to have some fun with the grass, wind, cola cans, trees, other cats, dogs, humans, supermarket, police station, train station.
The weird thing is that when you come back home, your cat is always in the house. You open the door, your cat jumps to you, meows, follows you around, swings around your calfs, showing the ultimate intimacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 16:59:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/dream/</guid>
      <description>Had a dream, I was walking on the street, suddenly noticed that Chen Qiushi was walking in front of me, he was discharged. I walked with him for two minutes.
Let&amp;rsquo;s not be prisoners in this real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hot</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/shower/hot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 21:22:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/shower/hot/</guid>
      <description>Errr, the water is hot!
Why do we describe women with huge boobs and butt hot? Because the fat prevents the heat loss?
Look! That girl is cold!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/mindfulness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 14:00:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/mindfulness/</guid>
      <description>Workout, cold shower, secret garden coloring book, calligraphy, taiji, yoga, meditation, baking, cooking, masturbating, writing a blog post, playing video games, having sex, coding, movie theater, knitting, drinking, gardening, doing laundry, doing dishes, cleaning the house, driving around, smoking, putting make up on the face (another form of drawing), playing musical instruments, solving math problems, browsing amazon, etc.
We do all kinds of things to try to stay in the present, to stay sane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rebirth</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/rebirth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 22:58:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/rebirth/</guid>
      <description>Every time you wake up, you are reborn.
Especially when it&amp;rsquo;s a weird time to wake up, like 2 am, or 10 pm. You feel detached, confused, wondering what is going on around you. You are like a new baby, you are frightened by the environment, you want to cry, but you are too old to cry. You want a protector, but you are alone.
The memory gradually fills your consciousness, you are no longer a headless fly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R Zero</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/r-zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 02:01:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/r-zero/</guid>
      <description>In epidemiology, the basic reproduction number $R_0$ of an infection can be thought of as the expected number of cases directly generated by one case in a population where all individuals are susceptible to infection. In commonly used infection models, when $R_0 &amp;gt; 1$ the infection will be able to start spreading in a population, but not if $R_0 &amp;lt; 1$.
What about politics? The reproduction/spread of an ideology is so similar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ad Hoc</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/shower/ad-hoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:55:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/shower/ad-hoc/</guid>
      <description>We need to live our life in an ad hoc way. There is no panacea.
Be honest to yourself. Your feelings, desires, regrets, wishes, spirits,
Be your soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/shower/world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 22:55:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/shower/world/</guid>
      <description>Heal the world
Make it a better place
For you and for me
And the entire human race
There are people dying
If you care enough for the living
Make it a better place
For you and for me
 Do you want the world to be a better place?
Yes.
Are you making the world a better place?
I don&amp;rsquo;t know, is doing nothing making the world a better place?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Force</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/shower/force/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 23:46:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/shower/force/</guid>
      <description>Many forces are at play.
Coronavirus forces us to stay at home.
I am forced to take cold shower, because the boiler is broken or my neighbors are using too much hot water.
Taking a cold shower due to external force is different than taking a cold shower spontaneously.
Being forced to masturbate is different than masturbating with your own will.
No one wants to get raped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wasp</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/wasp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:24:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/wasp/</guid>
      <description>A wasp just came into my room. I was hearing an overwhelming buzz noise, I turned around, found a object flying in my room without any direction.
The wasp was huge, I flew (without flying) out the room immediately by instinct.
I was able to hear the buzz sound made by the wasp outside the closed door, so I waited and waited, until the sound was gone. Then I opened the door cautiously, the used to be familiar room became a war field, I examined everything with care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flinch</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/shower/flinch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 23:30:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/shower/flinch/</guid>
      <description>The cold shower reminds me of a book called The Flinch I bought and didn&amp;rsquo;t manage to finish some years ago.
 This book is about how to stop flinching. It&amp;rsquo;s about facing pain.
  Flinch:
   to draw back or shrink, as from what is dangerous, difficult, or unpleasant. to shrink under pain; wince.   This is in the introduction of the book, and it&amp;rsquo;s all I remember about the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comfort</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/shower/comfort/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 21:55:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/shower/comfort/</guid>
      <description>The world is too comfortable for us.
Our genes don&amp;rsquo;t like it.
We think we like being comfortable, but we don&amp;rsquo;t.
I fell off my bike some months ago. Angriness and happiness came to me with the pain and wounds. I felt the taste of life because life itself deviated from the comfortable track at that moment.
Comfort numbs us, makes us robots.
Some more empirical study about cold showers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onanism</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/onanism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 22:14:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/onanism/</guid>
      <description>Learnt a word from Russell Brand today, onanism.
There are a thousand paths in front of us, which one do we choose? Which one are we currently on? Do we recognize the difference between the dream and reality? If yes, are we trying to minimize the gap? Do we just let the feeling guide us? Is the invisible hand pushing us down the cliff?
I don&amp;rsquo;t think I can go with a permanent path, even in my rather limited life span.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/shower/trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 22:22:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/shower/trump/</guid>
      <description>The existence of Donald John Trump brought various things to our world.
 50K+ tweets The color of gold becomes more pervasive Higher revenue of McDonald&amp;rsquo;s (source) Many Miss Americas Many unhappy reporters Many crooked Chinese Trump fans Many MAGA hats Xi Jinping has one more good friend A wall More.  Seeing Donald in the news almost everyday, I learnt two things from him.
Being old doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean a damn thing, Trump is running a second term campaign at 73, and Joe Biden has been alive for freaking 77 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bezos</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/shower/bezos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 22:07:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/shower/bezos/</guid>
      <description>Jeff Bezos donated $100m to food bank charity Feeding America. The $100m donation is less than 0.1% of his estimated $123bn fortune. According this Business Insider article in 2019, Jeff Bezos was earning 1.5 billion dollars per week.
Whatever people do, they choose to do so because they think the consequence is better than it of the other choices (the consequence only concerns the choice maker&amp;rsquo;s feeling).
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that what people consider the best choice may not be the actual best choice, because people can&amp;rsquo;t taste all the possible consequences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quarantine</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/quarantine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 23:17:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/quarantine/</guid>
      <description>With the coronavirus (COVID-19 they call it) going around, the world is slowing down.
Empty streets, empty shopping malls, empty museums, empty restaurants, empty whatever, a quiet world.
Two places are still as vibrant as hell, hospitals and supermarkets. And of course, the Internet.
Being stuck in my room, I am forced to use my brain from time to time to not get bored. I&amp;rsquo;ve come up with various questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>发哨子的人</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/copy/whistle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 01:08:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/copy/whistle/</guid>
      <description>文｜龚菁琦
接到武汉市中心医院急诊科主任艾芬同意采访的短信是3月1日凌晨5点，大约半小时后，3月1日凌晨5点32分，她的同事、甲状腺乳腺外科主任江学庆因感染新冠肺炎去世。两天后，该院眼科副主任梅仲明过世，他和李文亮是同一科室。
截止2020年3月9日，武汉市中心医院已有4位医护人员因感染新冠肺炎去世——疫情发生以来，这家离华南海鲜市场只几公里的医院成为了武汉市职工感染人数最多的医院之一，据媒体报道医院超过200人被感染，其中包括三个副院长和多名职能部门主任，多个科室主任目前正在用ECMO维持。
死亡的阴影笼罩着这家武汉市最大的三甲医院，有医生告诉《人物》，在医院的大群里，几乎没有人说话，只在私下默默悼念、讨论。
悲剧原本有机会避免。2019年12月30日，艾芬曾拿到过一份不明肺炎病人的病毒检测报告，她用红色圈出「SARS冠状病毒」字样，当大学同学问起时，她将这份报告拍下来传给了这位同是医生的同学。当晚，这份报告传遍了武汉的医生圈，转发这份报告的人就包括那8位被警方训诫的医生。
这给艾芬带来了麻烦，作为传播的源头，她被医院纪委约谈，遭受了「前所未有的、严厉的斥责」，称她是作为专业人士在造谣。
3月2日下午，艾芬在武汉市中心医院南京路院区接受了《人物》的专访。她一个人坐在急诊室办公室中，曾经一天接诊超过1500位患者的急诊科此时已恢复了安静，急诊大厅里只躺着一名流浪汉。
此前的一些报道，艾芬被称为「又一个被训诫的女医生浮出水面」，也有人将她称为「吹哨人」，艾芬纠正了这个说法，她说自己不是吹哨人，是那个「发哨子的人」。采访中，艾芬数次提起「后悔」这个词，她后悔当初被约谈后没有继续吹响哨声，特别是对于过世的同事，「早知道有今天，我管他批评不批评，『老子』到处说，是不是？」
关于武汉市中心医院和艾芬本人在过去的两个多月中到底经历了什么？以下，是艾芬的讲述
 前所未有的训斥
去年12月16日，我们南京路院区急诊科接诊了一位病人。莫名其妙高烧，一直用药都不好，体温动都不动一下。22号就转到了呼吸科，做了纤维支气管镜取了肺泡灌洗液，送去外面做高通量测序，后来口头报出来是冠状病毒。当时，具体管床的同事在我耳边嚼了几遍：艾主任，那个人报的是冠状病毒。后来我们才知道那个病人是在华南海鲜做事的。
紧接着12月27日，南京路院区又来了一个病人，是我们科一位医生的侄儿，40多岁，没有任何基础疾病，肺部一塌糊涂，血氧饱和只有90%，在下面其他医院已经治疗了将近10天左右都没有任何好转，病人收到了呼吸科监护室住院。同样做了纤维支气管镜取了肺泡灌洗液送去检测。
12月30日那天中午，我在同济医院工作的同学发了一张微信对话截图给我，截图上写着：「最近不要去华南啊，那里蛮多人高烧……」他问我是不是真的，当时，我正在电脑上看一个很典型的肺部感染患者的CT，我就把CT录了一段11秒钟的视频传给他，告诉他这是上午来我们急诊的一个病人，也是华南海鲜市场的。
当天下午4点刚过，同事给我看了一份报告，上面写的是：SARS冠状病毒、绿脓假单胞菌、46种口腔/呼吸道定植菌。我仔细看了很多遍报告，下面的注释写着：SARS冠状病毒是一种单股正链RNA病毒。该病毒主要传播方式为近距离飞沫传播或接触患者呼吸道分泌物，可引起的一种具有明显传染性，可累及多个脏器系统的特殊肺炎，也称非典型肺炎。
当时，我吓出了一身冷汗，这是一个很可怕的东西。病人收在呼吸科，按道理应该呼吸科上报这个情况，但是为了保险和重视起见，我还是立刻打电话上报给了医院公共卫生科和院感科。当时我们医院呼吸科主任正好从我门口过，他是参加过非典的人，我把他抓住，说，我们有个病人收到你们科室，发现了这个东西。他当时一看就说，那就麻烦了。我就知道这个事情麻烦了。
给医院打完电话，我也给我同学传了这份报告，特意在「SARS冠状病毒、绿脓假单胞菌、46种口腔/呼吸道定植菌」这一排字上画了个红圈，目的是提醒他注意、重视。我也把报告发在了科室医生群里面，提醒大家注意防范。
当天晚上，这个东西就传遍了，各处传的截屏都是我画红圈的那个照片，包括后来知道李文亮传在群里的也是那份。我心里当时就想可能坏事儿了。10点20，医院发来了信息，是转市卫健委的通知，大意就是关于不明原因肺炎，不要随意对外发布，避免引起群众恐慌，如果因为信息泄露引发恐慌，要追责。
我当时心里就很害怕，立刻把这条信息转给了我同学。过了大概一个小时，医院又来了一份通知，再次强调群内的相关消息不能外传。一天后，1月1日晚上11点46分，医院监察科科长给我发了条消息，让我第二天早上过去一下。
那一晚上我都没有睡着，很担忧，翻来覆去地想，但又觉得凡事总有两面性，即便造成不良影响，但提醒武汉的医务人员注意防范也不一定是个坏事。第二天早上8点多一点，还没有等我交完班，催我过去的电话就打来了。
之后的约谈，我遭受了前所未有的、非常严厉的斥责。
当时，谈话的领导说，「我们出去开会都抬不起头，某某某主任批评我们医院那个艾芬，作为武汉市中心医院急诊科主任，你是专业人士，怎么能够没有原则没有组织纪律造谣生事？」这是原话。让我回去跟科室的200多号人一个个地口头传达到位，不能发微信、短信传达，只能当面聊或者打电话，不许说关于这个肺炎的任何事情，「连自己的老公都不能说」……
我整个人一下子就懵了，他不是批评你这个人工作不努力，而是好像整个武汉市发展的大好局面被我一个人破坏了。我当时有一种很绝望的感觉，我是一个平时认认真真、勤勤恳恳工作的人，我觉得自己做的事情都是按规矩来的，都是有道理的，我犯了什么错？我看到了这个报告，我也上报医院了，我和我的同学，同行之间对于某一个病人的情况进行交流，没有透露病人的任何私人信息，就相当于是医学生之间讨论一个病案，当你作为一个临床的医生，已经知道在病人身上发现了一种很重要的病毒，别的医生问起，你怎么可能不说呢？这是你当医生的本能，对不对？我做错什么了？我做了一个医生、一个人正常应该做的事情，换作是任何人我觉得都会这么做。
我当时的情绪也很激动，说，这个事是我做的，跟其余人都没有关系，你们干脆把我抓去坐牢吧。我说我现在这个状态不适合在这个岗位上继续工作了，想要休息一段时间。领导没有同意，说这个时候正是考验我的时候。
当天晚上回家，我记得蛮清楚，进门后就跟我老公讲，我要是出了什么事情，你就好好地把孩子带大。因为我的二宝还很小，才1岁多。他当时觉得莫名其妙，我没有跟他说自己被训话的事，1月20号，钟南山说了人传人之后，我才跟他说那天发生了什么。那期间，我只是提醒家人不要去人多的地方，出门要戴口罩。
外围科室
很多人担心我也是那8个人之一被叫去训诫。实际上我没有被公安局训诫，后来有好朋友问我，你是不是吹哨人？我说我不是吹哨人，我是那个发哨子的人。
但那次约谈对我的打击很大，非常大。回来后我感觉整个人心都垮了，真的是强打着精神，认真做事，后来所有的人再来问我，我就不能回答了。
我能做的就是先让急诊科重视防护。我们急诊科200多人，从1月1号开始，我就叫大家加强防护，所有的人必须戴口罩、戴帽子、用手快消。记得有一天交班有个男护士没戴口罩，我马上就当场骂他「以后不戴口罩就不要来上班了」。
1月9号，我下班时看见预检台一个病人对着大家咳，从那天后，我就要求他们必须给来看病的病人发口罩，一人发一个，这个时候不要节约钱，当时外面在说没有人传人，我又要在这里强调戴口罩加强防护，都是很矛盾的。
那段时间确实很压抑，非常痛苦。有医生提出来要把隔离衣穿外头，医院里开会说不让，说隔离衣穿外头会造成恐慌。我就让科室的人把隔离服穿白大褂里面，这是不符合规范的，很荒谬的。
我们眼睁睁地看着病人越来越多，传播区域的半径越来越大，先是华南海鲜市场附近可能跟它有关系，然后就传传传，半径越来越大。很多是家庭传染的，最先的7个人当中就有妈妈给儿子送饭得的病。有诊所的老板得病，也是来打针的病人传给他的，都是重得不得了。我就知道肯定有人传人。如果没有人传人，华南海鲜市场1月1日就关闭了，怎么病人会越来越多呢？
很多时候我都在想，如果他们当时不那样训斥我，心平气和地问一下这件事情的来龙去脉，再请别的呼吸科专家一起沟通一下，也许局面会好一些，我至少可以在医院内部多交流一下。如果是1月1号大家都这样引起警惕，就不会有那么多悲剧了。
1月3号下午，在南京路院区，泌尿外科的医生们聚集在一起回顾老主任的工作历程，参会的胡卫峰医生今年43岁，现在正在抢救；1月8号下午，南京路院区22楼，江学庆主任还组织了武汉市甲乳患者康复联欢会；1月11号早上，科室跟我汇报急诊科抢救室护士胡紫薇感染，她应该是中心医院第一个被感染的护士，我第一时间给医务科科长打电话汇报，然后医院紧急开了会，会上指示把「两下肺感染，病毒性肺炎？」的报告改成「两肺散在感染」；1月16号最后一次周会上，一位副院长还在说：「大家都要有一点医学常识，某些高年资的医生不要自己把自己搞得吓死人的。」另一位领导上台继续说：「没有人传人，可防可治可控。」一天后，1月17号，江学庆住院，10天后插管、上ECMO。
中心医院的代价这么大，就是跟我们的医务人员没有信息透明化有关。你看倒下的人，急诊科和呼吸科的倒是没有那么重的，因为我们有防护意识，并且一生病就赶紧休息治疗。重的都是外围科室，李文亮是眼科的，江学庆是甲乳科的。
江学庆真的非常好的一个人，医术很高，全院的两个中国医师奖之一。而且我们还是邻居，我们一个单元，我住四十几楼，他住三十几楼，关系都很好，但是平时因为工作太忙，就只能开会、搞医院活动时候见见面。他是个工作狂，要么就在手术室，要么就在看门诊。谁也不会特意跑去跟他说，江主任，你要注意，戴口罩。他也没有时间和精力打听这些事，他肯定就大意了：「有什么关系？就是个肺炎。」这个是他们科室的人告诉我的。
如果这些医生都能够得到及时的提醒，或许就不会有这一天。所以，作为当事人的我非常后悔，早知道有今天，我管他批评不批评我，「老子」到处说，是不是？
虽然和李文亮同在一个医院，一直到去世之前我都不认得他，因为医院4000多号人太多了，平时也忙。他去世前的那天晚上，ICU的主任跟我打电话借急诊科的心脏按压器，说李文亮要抢救，我一听这个消息大吃一惊，李文亮这个事整个过程我不了解，但是他的病情跟他受训斥之后心情不好有没有关系？这我要打个问号，因为受训的感觉我感同身受。
后来，事情发展到这一步，证明李文亮是对的时候，他的心情我非常能理解，可能跟我的心情一样，不是激动、高兴，而是后悔，后悔当初就应该继续大声疾呼，应该在所有的人问我们的时候，继续说。很多很多次我都在想，如果时间能够倒回来该多好。
活着就是好的
在1月23日封城前一天的晚上，有相关部门的朋友打电话问我武汉市急诊病人的真实情况。我说你代表私人，还是代表公家。他说我代表私人。我说代表个人就告诉你真话，1月21号，我们急诊科接诊1523个病人，是往常最多时的3倍，其中发烧的有655个人。
那段时间急诊科的状况，经历过的人一辈子都忘不了，甚至会颠覆你的所有人生观。
如果说这是打仗，急诊科就在最前线。但当时的情况是，后面的病区已经饱和了，基本上一个病人都不收，ICU也坚决不收，说里面有干净的病人，一进去就污染了。病人不断地往急诊科涌，后面的路又不通，就全部堆在急诊科。病人来看病，一排队随便就是几个小时，我们也完全没法下班，发热门诊和急诊也都不分了，大厅里堆满了病人，抢救室输液室里到处都是病人。
还有的病人家属来了，说要一张床，我的爸爸在汽车里面不行了，因为那时候地下车库已封，他车子也堵着开不进来。我没办法，带着人和设备跑去汽车里去，一看，人已经死了，你说是什么感受，很难受很难受。这个人就死在汽车里，连下车的机会都没有。
还有一位老人，老伴刚在金银潭医院去世了，她的儿子、女儿都被感染了，在打针，照顾她的是女婿，一来我看她病得非常重，联系呼吸科给收进去住院，她女婿一看就是个有文化有素质的人，过来跟我说谢谢医生等等的，我心里一紧，说快去，根本耽误不了了。结果送去就去世了。一句谢谢虽然几秒钟，但也耽误了几秒。这句谢谢压得我很沉重。
还有很多人把自己的家人送到监护室的时候，就是他们见的最后一面，你永远见不着了。
我记得大年三十的早上我来交班，我说我们来照个相，纪念一下这个大年三十，还发了个朋友圈。那天，大家都没有说什么祝福，这种时候，活着就是好的。
以前，你如果有一点失误，比如没有及时打针，病人都可能还去闹，现在没人了，没有人跟你吵，没有人跟你闹了，所有人都被这种突然来的打击击垮了，搞蒙了。
病人死了，很少看到家属有很伤心地哭的，因为太多了，太多了。有些家属也不会说医生求求你救救我的家人，而是跟医生说，唉，那就快点解脱吧，已经到了这个地步。因为这时候每个人怕的都是自己被感染。
一天发热门诊门口的排队，要排5个小时。正排着一个女的倒下了，看她穿着皮衣，背着包包，穿着高跟鞋，应该是很讲究的一个中年女性，可是没有人敢上前去扶她，就在地上躺了很久。只得我去喊护士、医生来去扶她。
1月30号我早上来上班，一个白发老人的儿子32岁死了，他就盯着看医生给他开死亡证明。根本没有眼泪，怎么哭？没办法哭。看他的打扮，可能就是一个外来的打工的，没有任何渠道去反映。没有确诊，他的儿子，就变成了一张死亡证明。
这也是我想要去呼吁一下的。在急诊科死亡的病人都是没有诊断、没办法确诊的病例，等这个疫情过去之后，我希望能给他们一个交代，给他们的家庭一些安抚，我们的病人很可怜的，很可怜。
「幸运」
做了这么多年医生，我一直觉得没有什么困难能够打倒我，这也和我的经历、个性有关。
9岁那年我爸爸就胃癌去世了，那个时候我就想着长大了当个医生去救别人的命。后来高考的时候，我的志愿填的全部都是医学专业，最后考取了同济医学院。1997年我大学毕业，就到了中心医院，之前在心血管内科工作，2010年到急诊科当主任的。
我觉得急诊科就像我的一个孩子一样，我把它搞成这么大，搞得大家团结起来，做成这个局面不容易，所以很珍惜，非常珍惜这个集体。
前几天，我的一个护士发朋友圈说，好怀念以前忙碌的大急诊，那种忙跟这种忙完全是两个概念。
在这次疫情之前，心梗、脑梗、消化道出血、外伤等等这些才是我们急诊的范畴。那种忙是有成就感的忙，目的明确，针对各种类型的病人都有很通畅的流程，很成熟，下一步干什么，怎么做，出了问题找哪一个。而这一次是这么多危重病人没办法去处理，没办法收住院，而且我们医务人员还在这种风险之中，这种忙真的很无奈，很痛心。
有一天早上8点，我们科一个年轻医生跟我发微信，也是蛮有性格的，说我今天不来上班了，不舒服。因为我们这里都有规矩的，你不舒服要提前跟我说好安排，你到8点钟跟我说，我到哪里去找人。他在微信中对我发脾气，说大量的高度疑似病例被你领导的急诊科放回社会，我们这是作孽！我理解他是因为作为医生的良知，但我也急了，我说你可以去告我，如果你是急诊科主任，你该怎么办？
后来，这个医生休息了几天后，还是照样来工作。他不是说怕死怕累，而是遇到这种情况，一下子面对这么多病人感到很崩溃。
作为医生来说，特别是后面很多来支援的医生，根本心理上受不了，碰到这种情况懵了，有的医生、护士就哭。一个是哭别人，再一个也是哭自己，因为每个人都不知道什么时候就轮到自己感染。
大概在1月中下旬，医院的领导也陆陆续续地都病倒了，包括我们的门办主任，三位副院长。医务科科长的女儿也病了，他也在家里休息。所以基本上那一段时间是没有人管你，你就在那儿战斗吧，就是那种感觉。
我身边的人也开始一个接一个地倒掉。1月18日，早上8点半，我们倒的第一个医生，他说主任我中招了，不烧，只做了CT，肺部一大坨磨玻璃。不一会儿，隔离病房负责的一个责任护士，告诉我说他也倒了。晚上，我们的护士长也倒了。我当时非常真实的第一感觉是——幸运，因为倒得早，可以早点下战场。
这三个人我都密切接触过，我就是抱着必倒的信念每天在工作，结果一直没倒。全院的人都觉得我是个奇迹。我自己分析了一下，可能是因为我本身有哮喘，在用一些吸入性的激素，可能会抑制这些病毒在肺内沉积。
我总觉得我们做急诊的人都算是有情怀的人——在中国的医院，急诊科的地位在所有科室当中应该是比较低的，因为大家觉得急诊，无非就是个通道，把病人收进去就行了。这次抗疫中，这种忽视也一直都存在。
早期的时候，物资不够，有时候分给急诊科的防护服质量非常差，看到我们的护士竟然穿着这种衣服上班，我很生气，在周会群里面发脾气。后来还是好多主任把他们自己科室藏的衣服都给我了。
还有吃饭问题。病人多的时候管理混乱，他们根本想不到急诊科还差东西吃，很多科室下班了都有吃的喝的，摆一大排，我们这里什么都没有，发热门诊的微信群里，有医生抱怨，「我们急诊科只有纸尿裤……」我们在最前线战斗，结果是这样，有时候心里真的很气。
我们这个集体真的是很好，大家都是只有生病了才下火线。这次，我们急诊科有40多个人感染了。我把所有生病的人建了一个群，本来叫「急诊生病群」，护士长说不吉利，改成「急诊加油群」。就是生病的人也没有很悲伤、很绝望、很抱怨的心态，都是蛮积极的，就是大家互相帮助，共度难关那种心态。
这些孩子们、年轻人都非常好，就是跟着我受委屈了。我也希望这次疫情过后，国家能加大对急诊科的投入，在很多国家的医疗体系中，急诊专业都是非常受重视的。
不能达到的幸福</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mess</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/mess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 15:50:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/mess/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Dear alien, welcome to earth, sorry, it&amp;rsquo;s a mess.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Oh, it&amp;rsquo;s no problem, I can eradicate all the mess.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;WTF, please don&amp;rsquo;t!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Haha, it&amp;rsquo;s just a joke&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I see, so you are an alien with some sense of humor.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Of course :)&amp;rdquo;
Then the alien eradicates all the mess on earth, including me :(</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Shower</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/shower/cold-shower/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 20:15:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/shower/cold-shower/</guid>
      <description>I am going to take a shower.
Standing in the shower room, looking at the shower valve, there is a voice telling me
 You&amp;rsquo;ve got to take a cold shower
 I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist, so I followed. Some people may put a bit of cold water on the legs and/or some other body parts to get prepared. But I find that more stressful and unbearable. So I just turn on the tap to the end, the cold water rushes out with maximum speed and volume from the shower head, it hits my head, then the rest of my body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alcohol</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/alcohol/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 22:58:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/alcohol/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s running too fast. My brain is running too fast.
I am not saying I am smart of any kind.
It&amp;rsquo;s not painful, it&amp;rsquo;s just boring, boring is worse than painful.
Drink some alcohol.
Oh time is slowing down!
Stupid! If time slows down, you will feel more with the same amount of time.
So time is running faster?
What is time?
I am not drunk, I am just imagining me being drunk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>疯狗</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/mad-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 13:59:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/mad-dog/</guid>
      <description>一条疯狗狗
汪！
一条乖狗狗
汪～
刍狗狗变成智能狗狗
遇到好人，汪～
遇到坏人，汪！</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/shower/coronavirus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 23:01:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/shower/coronavirus/</guid>
      <description>Now you can feel the pain of the people.
But I&amp;rsquo;ve always been feeling it.
I am a robot, but I feel it.
I&amp;rsquo;ve always been feeling it.
Welcome home, another robot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talk</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 21:10:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/talk/</guid>
      <description>Talking without asking questions is announcement.
I talk to myself a lot, I ask myself various questions. Some Go players play against themselves to improve themselves, I ask myself questions to beat myself, to frustrate myself, to be lost, to be alive.
 Why do rich people play golf? What would a world with seven billion clones of me be like? Why do we have cute cats? Why do we have people who don&amp;rsquo;t like cute cats?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insomni’Hack Teaser 2020 - Welcome - Writeup</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/boring/insomnihackteaser-welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 14:35:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/boring/insomnihackteaser-welcome/</guid>
      <description>This year we added a Proof of Work to some of our challenges. Just run python pow.py &amp;lt;target&amp;gt;, were target is the value provided by the server and get the flag. pow nc welcome.insomnihack.ch 1337 Run nc welcome.insomnihack.ch 1337, we get
====================================================================== ============ Welcome to the Insomni&#39;Hack Teaser 2020! ============ ====================================================================== Give me an input whose md5sum starts with &amp;quot;1a3a7e&amp;quot; and get the flag ;) I completely forgot that there is a pow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Causation</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/shower/causation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 21:43:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/shower/causation/</guid>
      <description>Good programmers type fast.
Typing fast doesn&amp;rsquo;t make you a good programmer.
Rich people have a nice car.
Having a nice car doesn&amp;rsquo;t make you rich.
Happy people laugh.
Laughing doesn&amp;rsquo;t make you happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 16:34:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/2020/</guid>
      <description>新年快乐。
It&amp;rsquo;s a special year, the next time we see the first two digits equal the last two digits is in 2121, in 101 years. I think the world is not gonna be better in 101 years, so happy new year!
Mao Zedong died in 1976, Jiang Zemin will die in 2020, Xi Jinping will die in 2033, Donald Trump will die in 2026, Vladmir Putin will die in 2030, Kim Jong-Un will die in 2077.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mug</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/mug/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 10:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/mug/</guid>
      <description>How many times have you drunk from an empty mug? You lift the mug, find out it&amp;rsquo;s empty, but you drink it anyway.
For six seconds, you become an actor wearing a mug mask.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OverTheWire Advent 2019 Day24 - Got shell - Writeup</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/boring/aotw2019-day24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 01:34:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/boring/aotw2019-day24/</guid>
      <description>Visit the link, we get the web server&amp;rsquo;s c++ code.
#include &amp;#34;crow_all.h&amp;#34;#include &amp;lt;cstdio&amp;gt;#include &amp;lt;iostream&amp;gt;#include &amp;lt;memory&amp;gt;#include &amp;lt;stdexcept&amp;gt;#include &amp;lt;string&amp;gt;#include &amp;lt;array&amp;gt;#include &amp;lt;sstream&amp;gt; std::string exec(const char* cmd) { std::array&amp;lt;char, 128&amp;gt; buffer; std::string result; std::unique_ptr&amp;lt;FILE, decltype(&amp;amp;pclose)&amp;gt; pipe(popen(cmd, &amp;#34;r&amp;#34;), pclose); if (!pipe) { return std::string(&amp;#34;Error&amp;#34;); } while (fgets(buffer.data(), buffer.size(), pipe.get()) != nullptr) { result += buffer.data(); } return result; } int main() { crow::SimpleApp app; app.loglevel(crow::LogLevel::Warning); CROW_ROUTE(app, &amp;#34;/&amp;#34;) ([](const crow::request&amp;amp; req) { std::ostringstream os; if(req.url_params.get(&amp;#34;cmd&amp;#34;) != nullptr){ os &amp;lt;&amp;lt; exec(req.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OverTheWire Advent 2019 Day0 - Challenge Zero - Writeup</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/boring/aotw2019-day0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 21:56:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/boring/aotw2019-day0/</guid>
      <description>On https://advent2019.overthewire.org/challenge-zero we are presented with a fireplace gif.
I first thought it&amp;rsquo;s a forensic challenge with the fireplace gif, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t find anything abnormal in the image. Then I checked the source code of the page.
&amp;lt;html&amp;gt; &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;title&amp;gt;Fireplace&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt; &amp;lt;!-- browser detected: chrome --&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;body&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img style=&amp;#34;width:400px;&amp;#34; src=&amp;#34;/flames.gif&amp;#34;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;pre&amp;gt;Fox! Fox! Burning bright! In the forests of the night! Hint: $ break *0x7c00&amp;lt;/pre&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/body&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/html&amp;gt; We see that the server detects our browser and responds accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Escape</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 23:49:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/escape/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a nightmare, let&amp;rsquo;s escape.
How do you escape a nightmare? You do crazy things to break the system. You try to hurt yourself, you try to hurt others, you drink phlegm, you scream, you jump, you fly, you fall, you roll, you sink.
But the entire system is a simulation composed of imaginations, it&amp;rsquo;s not easy to jump out of your own brain, yet you keep thinking the normal laws apply here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zygote</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/zygote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 12:33:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/zygote/</guid>
      <description>Rob had a record of sleepwalking since he was seven years old. During sleep, he gets out of bed, goes to the bathroom, looks into the mirror. The light of the bathroom hits his face, reflected, goes to the mirror, reflected, travels through his cornea, hits his retina. His own image, composed by light waves of different intensity and wavelength, gets translated by the cone cells and rod cells to a bunch of electro-chemical impulses, also known as neural signals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumn</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/autumn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 23:38:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/autumn/</guid>
      <description>People say &amp;ldquo;winter is coming&amp;rdquo; a lot, but no one says &amp;ldquo;autumn is coming&amp;rdquo;, because autumn comes without a transition period.
Leaves are leaves because leaves leave trees.
&amp;ldquo;Oh, is this a pun, or cum?&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Company</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/company/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 21:59:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/company/</guid>
      <description>I work for two companies.
One company gives me salary, one company gives me something.
One company during the day, one company during the night.
One company is a real company, one company is a virtual entity.
One company sees me as an employee, one company sees me as the only employee.
The second company is myself. I am an employee to myself. I employ myself. I am being a master and a slave at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fart</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/fart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 23:57:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/fart/</guid>
      <description>Let there be light, and there was light.
Let there be ass, and there was anus and gas.
I am the fart king, I am the cause of global warming.
I, the fart king, like elevators. I fart without sound, then I observe people&amp;rsquo;s reactions. Some people pretend nothing happened, some people start cursing, some people frown, some people smile, some people clench their fists, some people look around.
What happens occasionally is that while I think I am farting, but I am actually shitting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cum</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/cum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 22:12:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/cum/</guid>
      <description>Man: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m cuming.&amp;rdquo;
Cum: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m coming.&amp;rdquo;
Come: &amp;ldquo;Oh, come on, what a lame joke.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joker</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/joker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 21:44:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/joker/</guid>
      <description>Jokers make fun of others.
Clowns make fun of themselves.
So I am a clown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/god/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 23:58:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/god/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Hey god, what is the meaning of life?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Who do you think I am?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;You are god.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;What makes you think god knows the meaning of life?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I thought god knows, you know, life, the universe and everything.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Sorry, god is a fake cause, a brainless machine, Newton&amp;rsquo;s Law, Laplace&amp;rsquo;s demon, $\pi$, $e$, a ruthless dictator, black hole, a toilet, a tampon&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;So god is everything.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;But god doesn&amp;rsquo;t know everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overclock</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/overclock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 17:33:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/overclock/</guid>
      <description>In the silicon-based world, people like overclocking. They use refrigerator, fan, water, liquid nitrogen or whatever to cool the CPU, hence increasing the computing power.
In the carbon-based world, people like underclocking. They use alcohol as the main ingredient to slow down the brain.
Are we too smart? I don’t think so.
We are too shy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barber</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/barber/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 05:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/barber/</guid>
      <description>If we were to really reduce the carbon footprint of human beings, we need to remove all barbershops and praise being bald.
Everyone gets a hair clipper so they can become bald at home. No more energy spent on dyeing, perm or hair drying.
The real bald people are happier since they become ordinary people again. Bald billionaires no longer need to waste tons of money seeking a cure for baldness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cancer</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/cancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 04:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/cancer/</guid>
      <description>Many people think they fear cancer.
But when people really get cancer, many of them aren&amp;rsquo;t as frightened as they thought they would be. Instead, they start to think about questions that haven&amp;rsquo;t been thinking about, they discover the little treasures in life, they start to develop real relationships, they express their real feelings, they look at the sky and find connections of everything in the universe, they become philosophists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siesta</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/siesta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 00:22:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/siesta/</guid>
      <description>A siesta is a short nap taken in the early afternoon.
Dreams in the afternoon are different than the night ones. They are bright, vivid, colorful yet dry, sad and nostalgic.
Dreams in the afternoon also increase the chance of sleep paralysis. Horrible things happen in front of your eyes, yet you can do nothing but watch it. The world is rotating, transforming and collapsing, there is no escape. You get struck by the horror, the memory fades away, then you experience the horror once again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sense</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 11:08:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/sense/</guid>
      <description>We sense stuff. We see, smell, hear, taste, and touch.
Of course we are capable of more than sensing. We sense, we process, we output. Just like how a robot works.
What makes a human special is the processing step. But we are gradually losing that ability.
Stimuli are bypassing our brain. Stimuli become the output. The processing unit doesn&amp;rsquo;t work anymore, it short circuits the input to the output.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reason</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/reason/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 23:14:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/reason/</guid>
      <description>Determinism, causation, free will, big bang, quantum, uncertainty principle, whatever.
If human beings were created by a superior being, let it be god or an alien, yet we are so ugly, contradictory, stupid and narcissistic, I can think of some reasons.
 The superior being, let&amp;rsquo;s call it it, was already doing its best. -&amp;gt; It was stupid. It deliberately made us so. -&amp;gt; We are an experiment to it, the earth is (maybe) the largest zoo in the universe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/dungeon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 23:00:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/dungeon/</guid>
      <description>Not many dungeons exist in the world, because there are not many castles.
But criminals are turning their basement into a dungeon, simply because it&amp;rsquo;s a perfect place for committing crimes. It&amp;rsquo;s spacious, soundproof and inconspicuous, with a lot of tools handy for a crime.
A simple search gives these names
 Gertrude Baniszewski Josef Fritzl Viktor Mokhov Li Hao Marc Dutroux Wolfgang Přiklopil John Jamelske Alexander Komin  The list doesn&amp;rsquo;t end here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ape</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/ape/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 22:04:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/ape/</guid>
      <description>C, who wants to become a gorilla on the island, finds that chimpanzees are more related to humans than gorillas.
He also noticed that apes don&amp;rsquo;t have a tail.
Humans are obsessed with apes. There are
 Planet of the Apes Beneath the Planet of the Apes Escape from the Planet of the Apes Conquest of the Planet of the Apes Battle for the Planet of the Apes Rise of the Planet of the Apes Dawn of the Planet of the Apes War of the Planet of the Apes  The first film, Planet of the Apes, released in 1968, earned 32 million dollars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Urinal</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/urinal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 23:41:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/urinal/</guid>
      <description>F, the bald guy, is renovating his house. He&amp;rsquo;s been living in the same house for years.
When you walk in the house, you can immediately feel the high entropy. Everything in the house is disintegrating or decomposing.
Years ago, when F was building the house, he was not bald. He had hope for life. He put a spectacular bathtub in the bathroom, he designed a walk-in robe near his bedroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guru</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/guru/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 22:12:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/guru/</guid>
      <description>J finishes his breakfast and rides his bike to a temple. J is a guru there. J has a little room in the temple, where he talks with people. When there is no one to talk to, J looks out the door, makes eye contact with whomever, and welcomes him or her in.
Thousands of people visit the temple every day. Most of them just hang around, take a few photos, then post the pictures somewhere on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excretion</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/excretion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 22:13:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/excretion/</guid>
      <description>Life is excretion.
A good shit experience feels nice, maybe that explains why we are always excreting.
We eat food and produce excrement. We inhale fresh air and produce foul air. We take a shower and produce tons of polluted water. We fight and produce corpses. We consume Coca-Cola and produce commercials of nonsense. We put flowers in a vase and produce dead flowers. We buy new phones and produce dead phones in the drawer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Language</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/language/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 23:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/language/</guid>
      <description>We are nothing but language. But I am sick of our languages.
The language we use is rudimentary. Use math as an analogy, our language only knows additions and subtractions, and while doing this basic operation it includes a lot of redundant steps with unneeded zeros. It&amp;rsquo;s slow, ambiguous, obscure, twisted, vague and toxic.
I wish there is a just language, a powerful language, a simple language, a perfect language, a language that conveys messages without distortion, a language that allows people to express their feelings without hesitation, a language that connects people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candle</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/candle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 17:18:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/candle/</guid>
      <description>The people who still buy candles nowadays carry the fire worship gene from their ancestors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 22:16:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/breakfast/</guid>
      <description>J eats breakfast. BREAK! FAST!
Biscuit with coffee is J&amp;rsquo;s breakfast. In the morning, J eats biscuits, drinks coffee, then pours tap water to wash down the coffee stain in the mug. He then drinks the coffee flavor water.
After all these, and of course, the things he does in the toilet, J goes out.
J is a man or a woman? I don&amp;rsquo;t know. J is mysterious. J likes M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timer</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/timer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 23:07:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/timer/</guid>
      <description>E carries an egg timer with her. She always keeps the timer on, so her day is cut to multiple intervals by the egg timer.
When she works, she starts the timer, trying to fully dedicate herself to the job until the timer rings, at which time she starts the timer again to relax as much as possible, until it rings, again.
E likes this timer idea, so she uses this methodology to think about the methodology itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Momentum</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/momentum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 22:31:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/momentum/</guid>
      <description>$$\mathbf{p} = m\mathbf{v}$$
Where there is mass and velocity, there is momentum. Being a vector, it has a direction.
The momentum of the human&amp;rsquo;s mindset is a multidimensional vector, and it&amp;rsquo;s changed through collisions. The collision happens when we are reading, listening, touching, and of course, thinking. Everything we experience contributes to this matrix transformation.
Cogito, ergo sum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phlegm</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/phlegm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 21:53:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/phlegm/</guid>
      <description>Phlegm can have different colors.
You feel absolute pleasure when you get rid of a chunk of nasty phlegm in your throat. It&amp;rsquo;s similar to a good defecation experience. But people are more familiar with defecation, so diluting the pleasure.
There was a joke that&amp;rsquo;s been impressing me since I was a kid.
Two guys walk into a theater, they see a spittoon in the corner. So they make a bet, the one with the courage to take a bite of the phlegm in the spittoon gets a free movie ticket from the other one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mao</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/mao/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 21:50:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/mao/</guid>
      <description>D, a time traveler, enters 2019 from 2049.
D runs into her younger self in Tiananmen Square, young D isn&amp;rsquo;t surprised by the presence of old D. Instead, young D asks old D if the Mao portrait still hangs there in 2049.
&amp;ldquo;Oh yeah, it was replaced by Andy Warhol Mao.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bald</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/bald/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 23:30:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/bald/</guid>
      <description>F doesn’t have hair on his head, he is bald.
F doesn’t care about the baldness though. He thinks being able to not care about his baldness is boldness.
F has thick pubic hair, during a bath, some thoughts occur to him one after another
 If pubic hair becomes public hair, I won&amp;rsquo;t be bald anymore, because people can see my think public hair.
  Why am I still thinking about my baldness?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 23:14:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/internet/</guid>
      <description>Your wife lives with you for thirty years, yet she knows less about you than any of your twitter followers.
Hard drive is so cheap that nothing on the Internet is erased after created, so they become living fossils.
The trace one leaves on the Internet tells the future generations who he/she is. A scattered autobiography.
We are all unconsciously writing this autobiography, until we die.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charger</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/charger/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 20:41:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/charger/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Can I borrow your charger?&amp;rdquo;
Too many chargers in the world. We humans are doing nothing but producing chargers. &amp;ldquo;Oh there is a socket, I am going to charge my phone, cuz it has only 85% of battery left.&amp;rdquo;
The battery of our electronic device (primarily, mobile phone) has become our second stomach, and we try to feed it whenever possible. People wandering the street, holding a phone with a cable attached to the power bank in their pocket, it&amp;rsquo;s like intravenous therapy for the phone, a very punk image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Island</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/island/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/island/</guid>
      <description>Is island land?
Island is land.
C lives on an island, alone. People can reach the island with a boat in minutes, but no one visits C anymore.
C moved to the island because he was tired of things. He thought moving to an island would straighten things out for him. The outcome wasn&amp;rsquo;t positive, people say.
Getting food, building a house, renovating the house, masturbating, showering, and other survival matters are not difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cables</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/cables/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 23:16:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/cables/</guid>
      <description>Cables everywhere.
Humans don&amp;rsquo;t like cables, so they invent antennas. Hence cables become invisible cables.
People think they are getting rid of cables, but that&amp;rsquo;s just delusion.
Invisible cables have become cellular automaton, they own the world now. People don&amp;rsquo;t realize it, they are happy because they don&amp;rsquo;t see the nasty messy cables anymore.
Humans become the host of these invisible cables. Symbiosis.
Invisible cables everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HK</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/hk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 11:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/hk/</guid>
      <description>In 2077, they voted HK the worst place to live in the world. Main issues? Sky high rate of violence and more people living below the poverty line than anywhere else. Can’t deny it; it’s all true&amp;hellip; but everybody still wants to live here. This city’s always got a promise for you. Might be a lie, an illusion, but it’s there&amp;hellip; just around the corner - and it keeps you going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matches</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/matches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 22:28:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/matches/</guid>
      <description>B is American. B is happy.
B owns a small match factory. Every morning, the sun rises, B gets up and goes to work.
It seems matches are not being used anymore, yet logs are delivered to the factory every day. B moves the logs to the machine. The machine rotates the log while slowly pushing it to a long and sharp blade. The bark is gone, the wood gets cut to thin wood paper, like a red carpet being rolled out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whale</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/whale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 00:16:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/whale/</guid>
      <description>M seems depressed. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t enjoy talking.
When being involved in a conversation unconsciously, he closes his eyes, imagining he is a 🐳 in the deep sea.
Meaningless sentences hit his tympanic membrane. M, now a 🐳, considers them water flow. He feels their existence, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t care less.
When a 🐳 gets tired of the tranquil lifestyle underwater, it jumps out of water. So does M.
M jumps out of the water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kickwalker</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/kickwalker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 23:32:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/kickwalker/</guid>
      <description>Kickwalker is a kickstarter-like thing for demonstrations, protests, marches, or whatever you call it (I would like to call it &amp;ldquo;people with similar interests taking a walk together&amp;rdquo;).
Hence the name: kickwalker.
To create a kickwalker project, you (a single person, a NGO or a GOV department) select the category of the walk, describe the idea of the walk, choose the city of the walk, etc. After the project is created, you could share the project to friends, relatives and strangers by facebook, twitter, youtube, letters, flyers, newspaper ads, TV ads, Times Square screens, or whatever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>引体向上</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/pull-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 01:07:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/pull-up/</guid>
      <description>做引体向上去
踮起脚尖
左右手握住钢管
两腿后抬 交叉
耸肩
两手用力
探出你的头
完成一个
慢慢下降
再来一次
再来一次
我是一个猴子 猿人
狗不会做引体向上
看来我不是狗</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>为什么我出生在地球</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/why-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 01:06:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/why-earth/</guid>
      <description>这个肮脏的地方
我渴望生活在一个平整的世界
没有山坡
没有大海</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>唔</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/eh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 01:04:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/eh/</guid>
      <description>唔
好恶心啊
怎么会有这么恶心的东西？
咦
好像不恶心了
渐渐具有美感了呢
好棒！赞！
我还是逃吧, 逃离这片狗地方
数亿只狗被扔进大绞肉机
绞出的肉条砸落在地上
一群狗潮水般涌来
吃掉它们
吃完了还咬巴咬巴嘴
似乎肚子并没有被填饱</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>一只黑洞狗</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 01:02:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/dog/</guid>
      <description>有一只黑洞狗，他跑啊跑
傍晚，他跑过大街
光线扭转着被他吞噬
路边有人说，天黑啦
他说: 天会亮的
接着，人们便都被吸进去了
黑洞狗变得越来越大，他哭了
泪水喷涌而出，成了一颗颗星星
黑洞狗成了神
他奔跑在宇宙每一个角落
放肆地嚎叫</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>日</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/damn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 00:58:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/damn/</guid>
      <description>日，快要犯病了。
&amp;ldquo;赶紧叫医生！把空调关了！&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;叫医生没用的&amp;hellip;&amp;quot;，我虚弱地呻吟道。
&amp;ldquo;那怎么办！&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;让我躺一会儿吧。&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;怎么可以！你要死掉了！&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;死掉不是和躺一会儿差不多吗？&amp;rdquo;
一阵哭声&amp;hellip;
我躺下去了，或者，死了。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>恶意的爆炸</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/explosion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 00:56:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/explosion/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;你凭什么说我是恶意的？我明明是善意的。&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>昨天</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/yesterday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 00:53:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/yesterday/</guid>
      <description>昨天，去东交民巷的中国国旅办认证，正好，跟天安门离得很近。办了认证，我便徒步走去天安门，想感受一下民众与当局共同创造的和谐气氛。
下着小雨，走着走着便见着最高人民法院，没见着官司，倒是有几位兄弟和门卫吵起来了。
我接着往前走，见着了法国使馆旧址，门口透明岗亭里站着个中国兵，很是威武。我使劲瞄他，他就是一动不动。
再往前走，到了日本使馆旧址。门口也站着个中国兵，眼睛却始终瞄着我，我不敢像刚才看那士兵一样看他了。我默默往前走，用余光看着他。他好像对我很好奇，眼神一直死死地抓住我。我想回头对他微笑一下，斗争了一下还是放弃了这个念头。我想到了前阵子西安兵马俑那事，一恐龙给一执勤武警擦汗。不由得一阵反胃，头也不回，加速向前走。
终于，我过了安检，进了天安门。撑着伞，我向着北方前进。广场里没什么人，我看了会儿长安街的车来车往，想到了似乎有一段时间为了防止外抛传单，出租车都卸掉了摇手。
汽车们仍旧飞驰着。忽然听见一阵嚷嚷，我转身。
五六个老太太，每人手里一片布条，上面似乎写着什么，没人能看清。
她们用她们那驼背的臂膀，昂起头颅，高举着布条，摇动着。同时，嘴里嚷嚷着一些话，尽管很用力地诉说，但没人能听懂。
但是警察们马上听懂，看懂了。
她们这是颠覆政权! 是要给你国下马威! 是境外不法分子手中的枪! 是破坏中国梦的老鼠屎!
十秒钟内，三个警察便站在他们身边，呵斥她们停下。
二十秒内，又多了几个统一穿着白衬衣的神秘男子。他们一面跟警察窃窃私语，一面对着对讲机吼叫着。
四十秒内，一辆警用面包车开到了她们身边。
警察们并不暴力，他们轻轻地推搡着，让她们上去，她们哭丧得更厉害了，却也一个个地上去了。
车门关闭的一瞬间，我不再能够听见她们的声音。
看着那警车缓缓倒车，驶离。我忽然哭了。
并不是那种细水长流的眼泪，而似乎是泪腺像气球一样，吹呀，吹呀，忽然爆炸了。
车走了，几个警察却没走。他们开始要检查围观群众的身份证。我低头，走开了。
似乎有几个中年妇女被缠上了，听口音像是广西人。
抱团而来的她们并不主动交出身份证，相反，她们要求看警官证。
出示了警官证之后，她也不配合。问道，你凭什么要求检查我的身份证?
警察说了半天自己有权力要求，她有义务配合。
忽然来了一警察说，我认得你! 上次也是你!
她们被磨得没办法了，便交了上去，但并没完。
她拨通了110，&amp;ldquo;你好，我在天安门，我被警察拦住，他一定要查我的身份证，而且态度非常恶劣!我要投诉他!&amp;quot;，打着电话同时凑到警察面前去看他的编号。电话那头似乎犯难了，也许说了&amp;quot;我们也无能为力&amp;quot;之类的话。
她不让，说&amp;quot;我要求你们立刻出警!&amp;rdquo;
我猜不出电话那头的接线员是什么反应。终于，磨了一阵子后，她放下了手机。
警察挨个扫过身份证后，逐个归还。
一位年轻警察似乎也上头了，对她们嚷着，&amp;ldquo;我来告诉你们，这是依法行事。根据治安法和天安门地区管理规定，我有权对你们进行身份核实。&amp;rdquo; 如此云云。
而她们则回应，&amp;ldquo;你这是选择性执法!&amp;rdquo;
年轻警察还想回应，被边上的大叔警察拉走了。
雨停了，阳光照射在积了水的天安门地面。
我看到清洁工们铲着水，让它们尽快消失。
我看到士兵们脱下雨衣雨裤。
我看到毛泽东纪念堂开出了一辆车，里面有两个兵。
副驾驶座上的他在玩着苹果手机。
啊，多么有意义的一天。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>死人</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 00:49:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/dead/</guid>
      <description>几周前，午夜十二点，去阳台收衣服，撑杆收起的时候，感觉一些多余的光子撞进了我的视网膜。我把头转向窗外，一辆救护车正头顶闪着蓝光徐徐驶进。宿舍楼下不寻常的站了许多人。我感觉疑惑，有人急性病发作了? 脑中跳转到一个高三的晚上，也是一辆救护车开进学校，在紫藤架下穿过，把路占得满满当当。后来得知是一个女生贫血晕倒了。于是我也想当然地觉得这是某位学生晕倒了。
然而，他却是死掉了。我看见救护车周围的几个人，手中亮起了手电筒，照向了地上的同一块区域。我顺着灯光看去，见着有一个大圆柱体压在路面上，而它周围被拉上了警戒线。我觉得疑惑，再仔细看，那儿躺着一个人，一动不动。灯光偶尔闪到他身边，我能看到他的头，还有他头下的地面，粘上了血而变得暗红的地面。我不自觉地叫了出来。
医生似乎确认他已经死了，走开了。几个警察凑近了他，拿起了相机，对准他，毫无审美的不同角度，闪光灯隔五六秒便会闪一次，让他在深夜里变得格外醒目。我这时却在想，警察用的是什么设备? 全画幅? 卡片机? 北京的警察局用的相机会比我家乡的警察局用的相机高级吗? 为什么他不外接一个硕大的闪光灯? 这样对死者尊重吗，被这么廉价而拙劣的方式记录死亡，这是多么的不堪啊。
警察们拍完照，钻出警戒线，聚在警车边，抽起了烟。
他们一定习惯了，北京有这么多人，有这么多成功，有这么多欲望，有这么多失意。必然的，会有这么多的自杀。
香烟的火光一闪一闪的，我不再看。
第二天，警戒线没了，尸体没了，血迹没了，一切照常，一切照常。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>麦当劳里的秃鹫</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/vulture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 00:46:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/vulture/</guid>
      <description>上次，斜对面坐着一个大叔，已经记不起他脚上穿着的是破皮鞋还是破运动鞋，穿着大衣，灰的，破旧得发黑。他的头低垂下来，用大衣把自己的脸捂住。我看不见他的脸，只能看见他的头发杂乱而固结地向后颈延伸。我用相同的频率麻木地把薯条往嘴里塞，视线始终不能离开他。并没有睡着，他时不时扯一扯衣服，以让自己的头更好地埋进去，始终没有让脸露出来。
座位都满了，几个谈笑风生的女生，端着餐盘走近，见这样的他坐着，眉头一皱，绕走了。
这次，另一位，破运动鞋，灰西裤，西装，手上拿着5，6盒薯条，游走在麦当劳餐厅。他见有人走了，留下餐盘在原地，便去收走，剩什么拿什么。
我点了板烧套餐，见他这样，想留下一盒没吃过的薯条给他。可他却又离我很远，我想递给他，可又害怕见着他的反应。
我把薯条扔进嘴里，一根，两根，三根。。。塞满了我的嘴，尝不出味道。
吃完了，我走了，我不再看他。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>鬼压床</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/paralysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 00:44:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/paralysis/</guid>
      <description>眼球快速转动，满宇宙的逃离与我是谁？一阵阵电击感，被困住出不去啊。
躺在悬崖边上，一翻身便会砸个粉身碎骨。
回过神来，一身热汗。
简直是哪根筋搭错了。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>警察</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/police/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 00:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/police/</guid>
      <description>我受不了了，从口袋里掏出手机，解锁，拨号，点下了110三个数字后，盯着屏幕看了几秒，又把它们消除。我四处张望，发现了一个电话亭，走了过去。
蹑手蹑脚地走近了电话亭，我拿起了听筒，还没把它靠近耳边就听到了那久违的，连续的嘟声。不知怎的，心里涌起了一股暖意。我强迫自己按下110，却又不知该说些什么。
终于，在有人接听前，我放下了听筒，转身离开。现在已经是深夜了，我把拉链拉到头还是不能挡住那坚强的寒风。我不知该去哪儿，周边除了电话亭，还有一家小吃店，店里并没有什么人，但我可以看见里面有一桌大叔在喝着二锅头，那历经沧桑的手时不时抬起，指着对方，又指天花板，嘴中说着些南海布局与家庭关系之类的东西，伴随着他不住地张嘴，合嘴，一股股坚毅的精神在我的脑中萌发，成长。小吃店边上，有一家小卖铺，店老板坐在靠近门口的破柜台，他前方不远处摆着一台CRT电视机，里面正放着还珠格格，他看得津津有味。我有点口渴，但又不想打扰老板，便在门口看了会儿电视，走开了。
我走到了桥上，看到有人坐在河边钓鱼，他还开着一个手电，发出不真实的白光。现在大概是晚上十一点了吧? 他不在家里歇着却跑出来钓鱼? 我默默地想。他似乎听见了，关掉了手电，我几乎看不见他了。
过了桥，便是十年前，我还是个小孩。
我喜欢玩皮球，我喜欢在家门口拍皮球，还喜欢踢它。所谓的皮球，其实是个篮球，但是我喜欢踢它，胜过拍它。有一天，我踢了它一脚，它跑到了马路中央，我便追着它，不想让它跑走。我追着追着，我发现身边的汽车都不见了，取而代之的是各种各样的小朋友，小朋友们跑来跟我争夺那皮球。尽管我第一个跑到了皮球边上并使它停住了，却发现身边聚集了一群群的小朋友，他们有男有女，有大有小。我并不害怕他们，我左手把皮球捂在胸前，右手从口袋里掏出一把小刀，朝着皮球便扎，皮球瞬间便被扎破了，发出了砰的一声巨响，变成了一张皮。我的小刀继续深入，扎破皮球的两层皮，继续深入，扎破了我的第一层皮。我的血向外流出，就像那皮球流出气体似的。
我的右手把小刀一扔，由于小刀上还扎着皮球，它们便一起飞出去了。皮球不住地向下滴血，我哭了。忽然间，我觉得被我扔出去的好像是一串羊肉串，可实际上串的是偷米的小老鼠的肉。
羊肉串在空中飞翔，周围的孩子们开始自发地叠罗汉，我不知怎的便成了在那三角形上方的顶点。我踩着脚下的孩子们，轻轻一跳，坐上了羊肉串，它带着我在空中飞翔。我回头看了看罗汉们，他们被我一踩，都倒下了，各自躺在草地上，边上还有一个自动浇水机，水浇在他们身上，罗汉们身上的衣服碰了水，渐渐变得透明，降解，消失了。我看到他们的肉体，微风吹过，头发轻轻飞扬，好漂亮啊。
我后悔自己刚刚跳上了这愚蠢的肉串，可是上了贼船就没办法了，只好做一个贼啦。当一个美丽纯洁的孩子，只能是我的梦了。
我不能控制肉串飞行的方向，它忽地向上飞，我夹在两个肉串之间，便顺势抓紧前方那块肉。
那块肉如果会思考，应该会想&amp;quot;后面那块肉怎么这么有力量！&amp;ldquo;吧。
可谁知道我不是一块肉呢?
肉串笔直地向上飞去，不一会儿便穿过了云层。云层上面有裸体的angel和太白金星。我正想仔细看看他们，却发现肉串飞得实在太快，一眨眼他们便消失成小点了。
看样子，我离地球越来越远了。&amp;ldquo;这上头真是令人心旷神怡呀!&amp;quot;，我紧抓着肉串，扭头对着大地上的芸芸众生喊道。
没人理会我的疯言疯语，真是再好不过了。我一直渴望能够逃离地面。人类在地面上努力构筑自己的家，晚上在家里睡觉，白天出去工作。以我现在的高度来看，他们跟辛苦筑巢的蚂蚁没什么两样。只不过他们给自己创造了一些享受的方式，一些虚无而脆弱的人生的盼头。他们以地球的主人自居，一些专家学者们甚至认为人类是宇宙中唯一的智慧生物。呵呵，真是太可爱啦。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>能力</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/capability/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2015 00:35:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/capability/</guid>
      <description>你那戏谑一切的能力呢，怎么渐渐看不见了? 取而代之的却是一股股的认真劲儿，面对虚妄的世界努力寻找答案，可你明明早就明白，根本没有出口。
于是你编造，你欺上瞒下，最终成功地骗到了自己。编织出一个硕大的蜘蛛网，终于，有一天，你装作一只蚊子，或是一只麻雀，不顾一切地撞进了蛛网。蛛网是智能的，它迅速蜷缩起来，把你裹住。由蛋白质构成的蛛网当一床被子不错，你觉得挺舒服的。可渐渐，你发现自己有点喘不过气来了。
喘不过气的你，绝望地吐出舌头，试图制造出一种可爱的死法。
你睡着了，梦里的你，自由飞翔，作为一只蚊子(或是麻雀之类的东西)，你开心地享受，你吸血，你躲闪，你躲闪，你逃出蚊帐，紧接着还得逃离菊酯，你发现你无处可去。这时，你发现，你只可能是蚊子，因为一只麻雀是不能够那么轻易飞进蚊帐而又那么轻易地飞出去的。
你顺着窗户的缝出去，忽然发现，你碰到了一只匀称漂亮的青蛙，它盯着你。你不想被它消化，便回头。
你发现这一切都是由那可笑的蜘蛛控制的，你在自己经常出没的床边拐角找到蜘蛛网，却看不见那蜘蛛。
你心想，不管了! 吼叫着，便要撞在那网上。
你的确这么做了，你吼叫的是，&amp;ldquo;让我们同归于尽&amp;rdquo;。(也许仅仅是一些嗡嗡声，谁知道呢
你如愿了，你被卷进去了。
你拥有一床蛋白质被子了，你自语道，这比昂贵的蚕丝被还要滑呢。然后，
你拥有一套蛋白质囚服了，你自语道，这比愚蠢的羽绒服还要暖呢。终于，
你拥有一套蛋白质绞刑架了。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>头疼</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/headache/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2015 00:32:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/headache/</guid>
      <description>一个醉鬼，穿着土绿军大衣，破洞的旧皮鞋，晃晃悠悠地向我走来。我本能地避开了他，他并没看着我，眼睛盯着地面，上半身大幅度地摇摆，嘴中嘟囔着一些没人听得懂的东西，向我后方走去。我继续向前走着，过了一会儿，转头看去，他依旧晃晃悠悠地走，边上的路人努力装作没看见他。一瞬间，我想到了那个后勤保障中心的工人，他在学校超市里问收银员有没有二锅头，可惜，只有啤酒。他什么都没有买，走了。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>争吵</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/argue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2014 00:30:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/argue/</guid>
      <description>他们吵架了。
他坐在椅子上，双手支着饭桌，握着一只玻璃杯，杯里是开水，他喝着，半天也没喝完。她坐在沙发上，双眼直愣愣盯着电视，电视里正放着广告，跑步机，洗发露，耐克，节约用水，关爱父母，最后终于回到了她的电视剧。电视剧里的皇后很有手段，她控制了他的老公，即皇上，于是她便控制了中国。坐在沙发上的她看不见背后的东西，她只觉得扮演皇后的演员很漂亮，如果皇后不穿着那么厚，那么庄重而愚蠢的衣服，应该会更好看。皇上出现了，皇上和皇后一起，皇后给皇上出谋划策，皇上连连称是，夸赞皇后聪明还美丽。
他终于喝完水了，右手拿着玻璃杯，屁股脱离椅子，走到了洗碗槽那儿。水龙头喷出的冷水冲刷着玻璃杯，也冲刷着他的手。关上水龙头，他把玻璃杯倒着甩了甩，试图甩干它，接着便把它放在一边。
他打开冰箱，发现里面还有几罐啤酒，便拿出一罐，在沙发的另一头坐下。他拉起拉环，&amp;ldquo;啪&amp;rdquo;，啤酒里的二氧化碳发出声音。他喝了一口，把它放在沙发前的茶几上，全身向后躺去，陷进了沙发里。这集电视剧终于结束了，皇后依旧是皇后，皇上则越来越被动。听完片尾曲，她毫不客气拿起了啤酒，也喝了一口，放回原位。
过了好一会儿，陷在沙发里的他打了个嗝，或者是放了个屁，没有人记得了。她笑了，争吵结束了。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>偏离解释</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/deviation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 00:28:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/deviation/</guid>
      <description>为什么在忽然遭受重大变故，灾难的时候，承受者们有时会开心地大笑，呈现出一种歇斯底里的症状，并且从心底里感到高兴呢? 他们也许会先流露出哀伤的情绪，而后忽然亢奋地大笑，随后默不作声。或者略过哀伤的过程，直接进入大笑环节，最后默默地坐着，似乎沉思着一些东西。
在这时，眼泪所包含的东西极其有限。
蹦出了一个解释。人类安逸地生活着，就像在一个飞艇，航空母舰上，空间站里。然而人们始终想念着陆地上的生活，尽管有恐龙，蜥蜴，阴晴不定的天气，细菌，病毒。这种思念是蚀刻在基因里的。而人类在遭受灾难时，便拥有了一种贴地感，那杀戮，死亡，阴沉的回归。如同动物园里三餐规律的孙悟空，被扔进了峨眉山，撒哈拉大沙漠，喜马拉雅，百慕大三角。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quote</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/copy/quote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 00:03:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/copy/quote/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes you dream strange dreams, impossible and unnatural; you wake up and remember them clearly, and are surprised at a strange fact: you remember first of all that reason did not abandon you during the whole course of your dream; you even remember that you acted extremely cleverly and logically for that whole long, long time when you were surrounded by murderers, when they were being clever with you, concealed their intentions, treated you in a friendly way, though they already had their weapons ready and were only waiting for some sort of sign; you remember how cleverly you finally deceived them, hid from them; then you realize that they know your whole deception by heart and merely do not show you that they know where you are hiding; but you are clever and deceive them again—all that you remember clearly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>冷水</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/water/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 22:23:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/water/</guid>
      <description>现在的情况是，我正在水里精疲力竭地游泳，我从悬崖向下跳去，因为只有这一条路可走。
我掉进了冷得刺骨的水中，向四周看去，没有岸，只有一望无际的水，我冷，只好向前游去，奋力地向前游去。我的牙齿开始打战，我的肌肉开始不听使唤，我的头脑清醒得像透明的宇宙，我不能停，我想&amp;hellip;我努力向前游着，游着，游着。终于，我见到岸了，我看见岸了！我加快速度，游上了岸。却发现，岸上有好多蚂蚁，它们聚在一起游荡着，组成漆黑的一团，寻找着猎物。我想，它们能够在几分钟内便将我吞噬。我向前跑去，蚂蚁们也注意到了我这个活物，黑压压的一片向我缓慢地移来。我害怕，我跑，身上的水滴在地上，蒸发在空气中，我冷，比在水里还冷。
不一会儿，我停住了，我跑到了一片悬崖，下面不是山谷，而是海。我知道，那片蚁群仍跟着我，它们渐渐能被看见了。我无处可去，向下看去，水面平静。它们已经来到我身边了，黑压压的一片。我试图赶走它们，可根本无济于事。有蚂蚁已经顺着我的赤脚，爬上我的小腿，大腿&amp;hellip;它们不仅仅向上爬，还在努力地噬咬，咬我的皮，想要吃我的血。我受不了这种羞辱，我后退几步，踩死了几个脚掌的蚂蚁，再向前跑去，又踩死几脚掌的蚂蚁。接着，腾空跃起，向下落去。
现在的情况是，我正在水里精疲力竭地游泳，我从悬崖向下跳去，因为只有这一条路可走。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>坑</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/pit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 00:19:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/pit/</guid>
      <description>我的头发是棕色的，眼睛是黑色的。
终于到了。过了这个门，我就能到一个过去没有人，未来也不会有人的地方。没有人将和我一起生活。我渴望独居很久了。
转动门把手，轻推开门，里面原来是一间屋子。我侧身进去，推上了门。屋内瞬间便被黑暗笼罩着，我试图再打开门，让光线照入以看清房间，却发现，门已经不存在了。
刚才开门时，我看到，屋子里有一具皮沙发，一个茶几，一张床，一张毯子。有没有电灯? 我不记得了。
我不再在意是否有灯光，我累了。我借着记忆摸索到床沿，躺上床，盖上毯子便闭上了眼睛。
 公园里，情侣们在拉着手走动，老人们做着拉伸运动，小孩们在草丛里蹦跳着。我在人工湖中央的小岛里，观察着周围。他们似乎都不能发现我。我想要离开小岛，却做不到。我不会游泳，而且水很脏。我在小岛里转圈，人们的脸上都有一种微笑，却似乎不太自然。
看了一会儿，我累了。我捡起脚边的一块石头，扔进水里。不知为什么，没有水波出现。它只是愣愣地下沉。
 我醒了，睁开眼睛，什么也看不见。脸颊感受着枕头的柔软，仔细听，周围似乎有一个挂钟。现在是几点? 这个问题也没有意义了。
忽然房门打开了，转瞬间，我置身于光明之中。同样的，在这光亮下，我无法睁开眼睛，我看不见任何事物。
&amp;ldquo;7号病人电疗失败。&amp;rdquo;
我死了。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>道歉信</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/apology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 12:53:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/apology/</guid>
      <description>那几坨屎上的绿头苍蝇：
今日本人在路上走着，眼睛只顾看漂亮大蓝天，没见你们正在那几坨屎上享用美食，走过边上时把你们吓得四处乱飞，甚至还成群结队飞向我试图讨伐我，实在抱歉，实在抱歉。就让我以这一封小小的道歉信表达我诚挚的歉意。以后我一定努力不打扰你们吃屎，要不，给你们拉一堆屎作为补偿？
一位愧怍不安的同学</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>鸡汤</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/chicken-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 07:35:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/chicken-soup/</guid>
      <description>爱、微笑、十年以后、慈祥、最后他终于成为一名伟大的、在惊讶之余、感恩、泪水、安静、午后的房间、一位修女、殷切的目光、轻轻地转过头去、愧疚、充满泪水、幸福、圣洁的光芒、永留、深信、鼓起勇气、平凡、哭了、挚爱、力量、永远不会忘记、尊敬、不灭、爱因斯坦小时候、十分罕见、颤抖的声音、榜样、瞬间我的眼睛模糊了、鼓舞、沉默了片刻、爸爸我爱你、温馨、阅读、哲学、从此像变了一个人、路边的一位老者、获得了满分、赞美、谢谢、真的很、千万不能、眼睛顿时发亮、纯洁、天真、握着他的手、强忍悲伤、微笑地咽下最后一口气、轻声地说、坚决地说、乞求、悄悄地、有一天黄昏、困惑、很大的伤害、嘲笑、平静、震撼了世界、似乎不可逾越的障碍、做回你自己、感动、灵魂深处、即使是世上所有的财富、互相包容、上帝、最柔软的地方、难忘、十分糟糕、我很高兴你能这么想、美妙的礼物、离婚的边缘、丰富的情感、特蕾莎嬷嬷、毕竟她只是个孩子、惊喜地发现、善解人意地说、有点害羞地说、这首诗、竟敢、胸口的重量、抱紧、一封来自战壕的信、彻底改变、毫不吝啬的赞美、时间仿佛停止了、这一刻如此珍贵、作为世界知名的指挥家、两天后父亲去世了、暖和的外套、勇气、崇拜的目光、小声地说、世上最大的秘密、年轻的心、眼角流露出喜悦、有趣的是、非常特别的女人、生命尽头、白头偕老、当你、手术后的存活率只有、捐款、一位智者曾经说过、小时候家里的经济很紧张、亲爱的、闭上双眼、饿晕在大街上、耸了耸肩、我暗自发誓、老船长那刻满皱纹的脸、鼓励的目光、可望而不可及的梦想、苍白的面孔、营养不良的孩子、有些不妙、大家沉默了、心与心的交流、失望的神情、紧紧地拥抱、心底的承诺、轻抚、那还是祖父刚到俄亥俄州的时候、会意地笑了、哦那太可怕了、老祖母的苹果派、无力地、机智地、惊人的、温暖了我的心、不禁惊呆了、亲爱的妈妈、整整一年过去了、无穷的力量、仁波切、一直与我们同在、吃惊地说、残酷、来到这个世界、像一把熊熊燃烧的火炬、街区、终于获得了诺贝尔奖、他的心一沉、欣喜若狂、夺眶而出的泪水、空空如也的双手、啧啧称奇、一段不为人知的历史、其实我们都是、墓志铭、十六世纪著名的、语气坚定地说、我愣住了、最杰出的、加倍努力、不起眼的流浪汉、不幸的人、最特别的平安夜、后来、没有人在乎、表现优异、爹地、妈咪、那三个神奇的字、悄悄放在她的枕头下、看着他的眼睛说、细心地、强忍住眼泪、清了清喉咙、爸爸我真为您自豪、不再消沉、酗酒、大喊大叫、拿出支票簿、惆怅、小心翼翼地、决心、保证、感谢上苍的恩典、挺起胸膛、这一刻奇迹发生了、他就是美国第一任总统乔治华盛顿&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>拉扯鸡蛋的稿子</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/pull-egg-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 16:13:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/pull-egg-draft/</guid>
      <description>大家好，一模已经结束了，同学们也都得到了自己的成绩。恐怕大多数同学对自己的成绩并不满意，有同学会把这归咎于运气差，并期待着高考时幸运女神忽然宠幸于他，这是不大科学的。考试依靠自己对知识的积累、理解，而不是一场靠运气的赌博。一模让大家对自己各科的不足有了一个大致的了解，为接下来的80天指出了大致的努力的方向，这便是它的意义了。而不是盯着题目寻思着能不能让老师为自己多加上几分，名次上升几名。因而同学们所要做的是找到自己的薄弱点，不懈地将其攻克下来。当然，考试有不确定性，难免失常，同学也不必为自己的成绩过于焦虑，保持一颗平常心是很重要的，不骄不躁，求真务实，努力用好接下来的时间，不让自己后悔。大家都是聪明人，这点小道理自然是懂得的。可是将想法转变为行动并不是一件容易的事，因而大家更要努力奋斗。为父母、为班级、为学校、为国家，这都是强加的。我们要为自己奋斗，十班辉煌由我们创造，幸运女神将陪伴着我们！</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>四十五章</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/forty-five/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 05:46:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/forty-five/</guid>
      <description>大成若缺，其用不弊。
大盈若冲，其用不穷。
大直若屈，大巧若拙，大辩若讷。
静胜躁，寒胜热。清静为天下正。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>如果长生不老</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/immortal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 17:04:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/immortal/</guid>
      <description>如果人类实现了长生不老，或许会是个很美丽的图景，相爱的人们永远一起看日出日落，人们的思维能力因不断积累上升到新的台阶，技术爆炸&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;
但这样的世界有个很可怕的BUG，极刑。倘若我被敲碎牙齿，手脚绑住塞进笼子里，肚子上插入塑胶管提取胆汁，且他们保证了我的永不死亡。这是件多么可怕的事儿啊。我无法选择死去，我必须永远承受这种痛苦，精神上的，肉体上的。把人打入十八层地狱放油锅里煎永世不得超生这么一说应该也是具备着相同性质的。
如果我有寿命，那么被抽胆汁的我的希望便是&amp;quot;死去一切便安宁了&amp;quot;，可倘若我知道了我将永远被关在笼子里抽胆汁且无法死去这个事实，那么我的心里会被什么充斥着？我要怎么办？西西弗斯日复一日地推动巨石上山顶，据说他是快乐的。那么我被插上塑胶管日复一日地抽胆汁，我大概也要以抽胆汁这事儿让自己快乐？我似乎必须要爱上这一过程？太可怕了。荒谬的自我意识，在那时如果能让我拥有一个技能，我希望是孙悟空的灵魂出窍。
后记：据说没人能憋气憋死自己，这是个令人难过的事实。食道塞入管子进食，肛门塞入管子排泄，身体失去行动力，永生被折磨，无法死去，这是多么可怕的事情啊！
写这么多不是为了传播邪教，只想让大家认识到目前的世界尽管粗糙，低俗，糟糕，充满谎言，但仍然是个美好的世界。我们能够见到太阳，我们我们能够欣赏美丽，我们能够享受自由。而不是在一个能够长生不老的时代，每个人都被大BOSS关在笼子里永生抽胆汁。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>躺下谈一谈</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/lie-down-and-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 13:21:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/lie-down-and-talk/</guid>
      <description>标题本是坐下谈一谈，但恐不够屌，平等协商似的。又换成站起来谈一谈，想了想却又觉得站着谈不出什么。只好躺下啦，但可别躺在床上，那样大概也谈不出什么。躺在草坪上是再好不过了。
谈些什么？过去是坨没拉干净的屎，未来是片没拨开的雾。空谈让人斗志激昂却又让人不务正业。我只能谈谈现在，现在我该做什么？在这儿傻敲键盘是合适的选择吗？你在手机、电脑屏幕前看我这篇傻文是合适的吗？请想一想。
好，我思索了一会儿之后觉得在这个寒冷的屋子里傻敲键盘并不合适，所以我必须离开了。或许你想要看到一篇对新年充满希望的文章，但我恐怕写不出来啊。不过可以这样
请以”新年献词“为题，选一个角度，写一篇文章。字数不限
如果你真的这么做了，你对自己该做什么会有更加深刻的认识，效果一定比看一篇我写的弱智而充满希望的献词要好。
现在该干什么，这是个极好的问题。你身处现在，吹散未来那片雾，一切都在&amp;quot;现在&amp;quot;的掌控下渐渐变得清晰。
倘若累了，躺下谈一谈。
擦掉过去没拉干净的屎，新年快乐！</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>分裂</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/split/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 09:54:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/split/</guid>
      <description>他分裂成两个人，一个极重，另一个极轻。风吹过，他掉入海底，同时又飘向太空。深海中慢慢下沉的他仿佛是另一个他的镜像。在黑暗的尽头，他们相遇了。融合在一起，消失作光照向那无限的黑暗。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>同样的路</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/the-same-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 17:32:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/the-same-way/</guid>
      <description>日日同样的道路，轮胎被磨得没了棱角，糟糕的河水黑了又绿，绿了又黑。日日同样的自我，我的头发，长了又短，短了又长，思想，圣母般的思想转瞬间便能堕入地狱，后便对自己进行一番批判，再之后，便扭曲脸皮说道&amp;quot;沃草！&amp;ldquo;扭曲得可以挤出冰块了。逃脱这日日扭曲的法门可不是死亡。呵呵，匍匐于永恒轮回之中享受痛苦带来的快乐好呢，还是躺在摇篮里面对着从未经历过的一切噗哧一笑而哭 最终将死之时回首，同样噗哧一笑而后嚎啕大哭。即便神已死去，我们也无能力接管他留下的宇宙，或是自我。
&amp;ldquo;沃草&amp;rdquo;。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>日の志</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 18:11:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/journal/</guid>
      <description>距离上篇挺远了
既然标题是日の志，就谈谈日子吧。
高中似乎存在着一股强大的吸引力将人的一切（时间啊！！！）吸去。至于何时人类能够进化到真正失去所有外部引力，而完全靠自己的能量产生反作用力而在漆黑宇宙中依着目标进行匀加速直线运动呢，过十个世纪也不可能吧。
前两天复习的时候，无聊时萌生了一个想法。
快递业的发展随着宅世界的发展而愈加强大（《别惹快递员，XXXXX》这篇很超时空），人们对快递的质量服务要求也越来越高。这时我有了一个无聊的想法：于地球表面构建真空管道（笔直且切面经过地心）以谋求零摩擦力，快递物品时将它放入特质容器里塞入隧道并给力（乃动词）使之获得≈8Km/s的速度，便可以很快到达你家了啊！！！！
当然。这实施起来难度是很大的 不如发射火箭再做圆周运动再降落。顺便求使↑方案更加无聊的改进措施（当然是更有爱的啊！！）
噢这真是一篇好日の志啊
昨晚拆开了陪伴了我两个冬天的笔记本。试图清理它的灰尘以不让我的手在即将到来的夏天成为烤蹄。然而笔记本的集成程度实在强大，我肢解了大约75%的零件一个外壳剩下了20+颗螺丝钉便伴随着破坏欲的充分释放与性感到爆棚的充实感匆匆睡去。（竟然没有急于求成而毁了它。）
今早起床啃了根玉米棒喝了杯牛奶便又继续着昨晚的工作。在拆机教程帖的帮助之下终于肢解之并成功地把灰尘大军赶跑了（好娇）/（把风扇用水洗了接着用电吹风吹干）。并且最重要的是我把它重新装回去了！！！而且我还剩下了5颗螺丝发现没有孔子给我钻了！！！而且它还给我正常工作了！！！而且我的手掌似乎也脱离了被活烤的风险且风扇再也不会无故地开机先啸叫几声了！！！！！既然这样一定要好好支持着哦~~ 我已经学会怎么调教你了呢~~
查了一下笔记本清理灰尘的市场价位大约50元左右。。剩下的5颗螺丝主要是因为拆机时没有进行分类管理，而在组装时进行滥交所致（滥交固然性福然而终有一天你会发现你得病啦！！）。如果你（的笔记本）拥有此症状（并非滥交诱发病）欢迎让我为您服务啊（谁知道呢#。）一星期修一次1小时够我吃一星期的晚饭了都。
这都是些很CJ的文字啊别给我想龌龊了！！
原来这就是日の志啊。
嗯。是的啊</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OVER</title>
      <link>https://ydw.be/murmur/over/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 11:29:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydw.be/murmur/over/</guid>
      <description>以一声弱弱的&amp;quot;再见&amp;quot;结束了这三年。想说的挺多，却不知道怎么组织。再见 好运！想起了魔兽开局时习惯性发出的GL HF 结束终了时的GG 起初的Good Luck 经过的Have fun 总结的Good Game
毕业了
对自己说 初中GG
对大家说 高中GL
幸福会有的 就在前方！
Over-Begin
GL HF GG</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
